{
    "id": "3def6485b7f54d3b843f64bdf0da302a",
    "title": "Other, Another Or Others",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "47840e6fde954577911800f46d3fbbe9",
            "title": "Other, Another And Others",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Could I have .......................... piece of cake?",
                    "description": "Another means extra or additional.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "more"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has bought ........................... watch.",
                    "description": "Another means extra or additional.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must love one ...........................",
                    "description": "We use another in the expression 'one another'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The two brothers love each ..........................",
                    "description": "We use other in the expressions 'each other'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like .............................. cup of tea.",
                    "description": "Another is used with singular countable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you like .............................. rice?",
                    "description": "We use more with plural and uncountable nouns. Another and other are not possible.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "some more"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ................................. students have gone home.",
                    "description": "We use other before a plural noun. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where are the .............................. books you borrowed from me?",
                    "description": "Other can mean besides this or these",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't like these. Have you got any ............................. colors?",
                    "description": "Other has no plural form before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is writing ............................ book.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You never think of ............................",
                    "description": "When other is used without a noun, it is used in its plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The meeting has been postponed. You must inform the .............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}